The end. Thank you for watching.
And a gichi page from the session. Just a gichi page.
Highlights of my life
Seeing the buzz of your tweets on Mongichiyakiri.
I remember the day I met you.
I was listening to this song with earphones in
Counting from now on, how many years is today?
Highlights and a glass of whiskey in the kitchen
A family scene like any other
I waited for you to come home at seven o'clock with a bottle of lye bread.
A family scene that could be anywhere
At a friend's appointment
Distant night in Tokyo
Hehe, it goes by so fast
The distance that I love
It's always here
Sometimes people say if only we could turn back time.
But no one can fix it, no one can fix it, it's always been like that, well, it can't be helped.
The path ahead is deep and unstable, but it's not enough to be unsteady.
If only I could get into a time machine and become a traveler...
Shibuya, Shibuya
5000 Simpson
2000 Steve
2000 Gold
2000 Zlightly
top
However, it's not
Half-baked
Concepts
11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 2 4
11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19
I'm going to go live.
Yes, sir.
Okay, everybody, please, let's go live!
Production! Production!
Here we go.
On my count!
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve.
The smallest page of your youth is just a small page.
The highlight of my life
I look at the tweets of Mongichi and Kiri, and I remember the day I met you.
I remember the day I met you
I was listening to this song with my earphones down
I'm gonna count down the days, and I wonder what today will bring.
Highlights and a glass of whiskey in the kitchen.
Family scene like you'd find anywhere else.
"Come home at 7:00." I was hooked on live music.
It's a typical family scene.
I'm on a friend's schedule.
I OK?
7 o'clock. Far away.
It's always here.
It was interesting, wasn't it?
It was interesting.
There are not many works that are this elaborate or on this scale, so it was a lot of fun.
I was very particular about it.
I thought "Heaven" was a great name.
And I was surprised that the father was younger than me.
What about you, Mr. Yamazaki? I don't know.
I thought he was cool.
He's funny.
But I don't think I've ever met a father like him.
He's a stylish and sophisticated father.
And the scenes where they're working together...
He really cares about his daughter.
He's watching over her from afar.
He's a kind father.
It was wonderful.
He was a rebellious type of father, but he had a strong rebellious period, so when I was in the fifth grade, we fought every day, and my mother left the house.
That's how it was in my family.
So you are allowed to talk about such things?
Not at all, not at all.
We are very close, so there were times in the past, but....
Generally, girls and mothers are very clear about whether or not they will see each other, aren't they?
Yes, that's right.
We are good friends now.
My hometown is Okayama, but I have relatives in Kobe, and I used to visit them during summer and winter vacations.
I took the train to their house, and that was the only time I ever took the train.
So I had my mother take me to the station, and when I was in elementary school, I cried every time I had to say goodbye to my mother.
I went to Kobe, lived there for about a month, and cried again when I saw my relatives outside the train window on the way back to Okayama.
It was not so much that I went to a distant city, but rather that when I entered the ticket gate, I had to put in a child fare ticket, because I was a child.
The ticket made a beeping sound, and since I was a rather tall child, I was always suspected by the station staff.
I was always suspected by the station staff because I was a very tall child. I remember it well.
In Yokohama, there was Aki-Karen, wasn't there?
There was a Christmas market on Christmas Eve with one of the members, Hikaru Morita, so we went there together.
We went there together. We went there privately.
The old streets and buildings are still there, and it is a town that is suitable for filming.
That is why I have often filmed in Yokohama since I was young.
So I have the impression that Yokohama is that kind of town.
It is a picturesque town.
There are many picturesque places in Yokohama.
Yes, there are.
When you go back to Osaka, do you ever go through a tunnel in Shiga Prefecture and suddenly there is snow on the ground?
Yes, there is. Suddenly there is a snow zone.
I like that. It's like the world changes in an instant.
When I was little, I had a bento box shaped like a bullet train, and I used to enjoy eating it every time I got on the bullet train. I was sure to eat it.
You mean it was an ekiben?
Yes, it is. It was an ekiben for children, but I really liked it because it was delicious and looked cool.
Do you take it home with you?
Yes, I will.I take it home with me.
It's a very special feeling.
It accumulates.
It accumulates at home, doesn't it?
Yes, it does accumulate. It did accumulate.
You will never use it again, though.
I will never use it again.
Everything is fine with one piece, right?
I'm sorry.
I'm going to do it, after all.
I thought it was very stylish, and I thought it would be great if the music was combined with the images we shot today.
You can feel the passage of time.
The counts were made very precise this time, so it would be very interesting if they fit perfectly.
I think it will be a very interesting video if it fits perfectly.
I'm really looking forward to it.
The theme of this film is family, and the family of parents and children.
In that sense, I think it will be a perfect fit.
My family likes to sing karaoke.
Whenever we go home for New Year's, we always go to karaoke and sing and dance.
I think that is our usual family style.
You seem to get along with each other pretty well.
We get along well.
We have two tongues, so it's like they sing all the time.
How can you sing in front of your parents?
You can't sing?
I can't sing in front of my parents, it's too embarrassing.
I'm so embarrassed.
Who else can sing? Anyone else?
Who can sing in front of their parents?
Come on, come on, come on.
No? No?
Not a single one.
Oh, you sing and dance?
Wow, that's a great family.
No, but that means they're close.
That means they get along well with each other.
I envy you.
Do you sing your own songs?
I was told to sing.
But they took the microphone away from me, and the two tongues sang.
All the time.
How about you, Mr. Odawara? A family scene.
I've never heard a better story.
Family Scenery
This time, I used 24 frames of a father and daughter.
I don't have a daughter and I'm a man.
I don't have a daughter, and I'm a man.
but I can relate to it somehow.
I'm sure all male parents
I'm sure your daughter can relate to it too.
It's a bit of an exaggeration to say that it touches me.
But there's something about you that makes me feel a little bit tender.
I think everyone can relate to it.
The 24 Odawara queens were amazing.
In fact, I was pulling them towards the other side of the room.
Like today.
It was a strange experience.
It was interesting.
I'd love to see the full story.
I would love to go see the moment I was born, or the moment my sister was born.
I think I can only see the moment of birth in pictures.
I think I can only see the moment of my birth in pictures, so I'm curious to see it on film.
I think this is a wonderful movie that shows our daily life and the trains that accompany it.
I hope many people will watch it.
As a daughter, I could really relate to the role, but I did my best to play the role of a story of growth and upbringing.
I hope that you will pay attention to the next movie to see the changing relationship between father and daughter, and I think it will be very interesting.
I think it will be very interesting, so I hope you will watch it over and over again, down to the smallest detail.